[theme song playing]
[in English]
♪ You're driving alone at night ♪
♪ Deep in the silence
But it doesn't mean you're lost ♪
♪ And I'll tell you what ♪
♪ We're on the train ♪
♪ I promise I'll be where you are ♪
♪ If any thought is against you ♪
♪ With you, I am starting over ♪
♪ We're learning to walk again ♪
OUR UNWRITTEN SEOUL
[song concludes]
[Ho-su's father in Korean]
Ho-su. Doesn't your neck hurt?
DESTINATION
IAN MEMORIAL PARK
[chuckles]
I guess this attitude
is typical of an eighth grader.
You're not even responding.
I'm going to tell your mom later.
Which mom?
Ho-su.
Someday, you're also
going to make someone miserable.
There will definitely be a moment
when you cause the person
by your side to lose.
But you know, Ho-su…
Love isn't about winning or losing.
It's about--
[tires squealing]
[doctor] You've been through a lot, Ho-su.
But in my opinion,
it's pointless for him
to have any more surgeries.
What do you mean, Doctor?
[pensive music playing]
We should still do everything we can--
[doctor] Ma'am.
You recall Ho-su's condition
right after the accident, don't you?
Just the fact that he's alive
and walking again is a miracle.
It's time for Ho-su
and the rest of us to face the truth.
Ho-su will never fully recover
from the accident.
There are ducks here!
- Did it swim away? Where is it?
- Hey, a duck!
- It's a duck.
- A duck.
Yes, really.
[doctor] The best we can do right now
is to maintain his current condition.
He can't run.
He should avoid any strenuous exercise.
No hiking, no long walks.
[music concludes]
[teacher] The hike up Dusonbong Peak
before becoming seniors,
the biggest event of your lives,
has been our long-standing tradition.
- Mi-ji, want to race to the top?
- [teacher] To train your body and mind…
- Winner gets 10,000 won. Deal?
- …and your dedication to studying…
- Jeez.
- …at your final crossroads.
Is it really okay for me
to keep taking your money?
- [young Seung-hyeon scoffs]
- You wanna bet?
[teacher] …so you can soar even higher…
Don't fool around and get hurt.
We'll be checking
to see if all of you reach the top.
Don't try to cheat by coming down
before reaching the top.
[students] Yes, sir.
Those who aren't feeling well are exempt.
You can stay over there
with the school nurse.
[pensive music playing]
Are you sure
they're not exempt for being smart?
[whistle blows]
Get going!
[students chattering]
[Mi-rae] Where are you going?
Dusonbong Peak.
What for?
You're being self-absorbed.
No one cares
whether we go up there or not.
Stop making a big deal out of it.
- [birds chirping]
- [pensive music continues]
[Mi-ji] Ho-su!
[music fades]
I'm surprised you're here.
Are you also going to the top
to wish for good CSAT results?
[pants]
Why did you come back down?
The others said you were coming up,
so I wanted to see for myself.
Do you want some water?
DUSONBONG PEAK
NOKYEONG WATERFALL
Hey, do you want to use this?
It seems useful.
Hey, hiking is all about the gear.
Here you go.
What's going on?
You already reached the top?
No, I'm just running away.
Seung-hyeon is at the top right now,
and he said no one is checking.
[pants]
Mi-ji, if you don't hurry,
you're gonna be last.
Okay.
Go on ahead.
No, I don't want to break a sweat
when I'm not even training.
Just go.
It's fine. Let's go together.
Please just go!
[pants]
[soft pensive music playing]
[pants heavily, mutters] Damn it.
[Mi-ji] Your first love is Mi-ji?
[soft pensive music continues]
Why are you acting all surprised?
I thought you knew.
I did?
But you definitely…
Wait. Since when?
What do you mean?
No one decides when to start
falling in love for the first time.
You must have some idea
of when or why you fell for her.
Dusonbong Peak.
Dusonbong Peak? The mountain?
[music fades]
You mean the one the whole school hiked?
- [cell phone buzzing]
- Yes, if I had to pick a time.
- Hey…
- [soft quirky music playing]
Hold on. Hello?
Yes, I'll be right there.
Oh… [sighs]
[cell phone beeps]
- That mountain--
- Let's go.
Wait. Hey!
Wow. Dusonbong Peak? Me?
Me? Seriously?
EPISODE 5
ALONE WITH YOU
[music concludes]
HO-SU
[sighs] The more I think about it,
the weirder it is.
He liked Mi-rae, though.
[soft intriguing music playing]
You came, though.
You came and left with Mi-rae.
- Am I wrong?
- You're right.
[Mi-ji] That's what he said.
Why is he suddenly claiming
I'm his first love?
SINCE WHEN? JEALOUSY?
Don't tell me he's trying
to make Mi-rae jealous.
[inhales]
And what's with Dusonbong Peak?
[sighs] I can't even ask him outright
what he meant.
[Tae-gwan] This is the Planning
Coordination Department.
[music concludes]
The Digital Innovation Team.
[team 1] Hello.
[Tae-gwan]
The Corporate Relations Team.
[team 2] Hello.
And this is the Planning Strategy Team.
What are you waiting for?
Say hello to the CEO.
[team 3] Hello, sir.
Is this the team in charge
of the new HQ project?
Yes, our team is taking care
of all the minor tasks,
such as securing the site
before the construction--
The site issue isn't a minor task.
Yes, you're right.
Every task is important. I--
No, they're not all important.
[suspenseful music playing]
[chuckles]
I'm just spouting nonsense
because I don't know much.
As you all know,
I don't come from a public corporation,
so I'm not up-to-date on the new HQ
and how things work around here.
- Mr. Shin.
- Yes, sir.
You didn't give him a separate report
on the new HQ project?
Ms. Yu, is the report ready yet?
Pardon?
I'm sorry. The employee in charge is--
It's my fault, sir. I'll tell them
to get it ready as soon as possible.
Okay, then.
Good work, everyone.
[employee] Thank you, sir.
[music concludes]
Mi-rae. You heard him, right?
Get the project report ready by next week.
Pardon?
- Sir.
- [quirky music playing]
I can't make a project report
by myself in just a few days.
Come on. That report should be
a piece of cake for you.
Then can you at least assign
one more person to help?
You joined this project knowing
it was confidential, didn't you?
- But…
- Well?
Why did you accept it in the first place?
Wasn't it because you wanted
the reward all for yourself?
So do the work by yourself.
If you can't, then say so.
The penalty will be all yours too.
[Mi-ji breathes deeply]
[whimpers]
- [music concludes]
- [Se-jin] It looks so pretty.
How should I repay you
for giving me such a precious gift?
What goes well with strawberry jam?
Scones! I should make scones.
Let's get the scone ingredients first!
But we… [sighs]
You're lasting a pretty long time.
At this rate, this strawberry farm job
is going to be your longest gig.
Right.
Getting paid 200,000 won a day
is a pretty sweet deal.
But what if you were offered a job
that pays 250,000 won right now?
We're organizing our warehouse next week.
Plus, it's not just for a day.
Four days!
That's a total of one million won.
[cheers]
What's with that reaction?
Did your blood sugar just spike
because the offer was too sweet?
Oh, me?
You want me to organize the warehouse?
So should I pay myself to organize it?
Put your muscles to good use.
Oh, but…
it's a really important time
for the strawberries right now.
What do you mean?
So you're turning down a job
that pays 250,000 won a day?
Are you really Mi-ji?
I would love to organize the warehouse.
But I need to finish up
what I started, so--
What's with that pointless sense
of responsibility?
It's just a temporary job.
[Se-jin] "It's just a temporary job"?
[quirky music playing]
Did you miss the village chief's warning
about not poaching other people's workers?
Why do you keep sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong?
And you stole my worker first.
She almost became our store's
assistant deputy manager.
That's a ridiculous job title.
Why are there so many job titles anyway?
Plus, she's my business partner.
Your "business partner."
- Are you willing to give her some land?
- I can. Can you?
Did you get one of these?
- What is that?
- [in English] Oops.
[in Korean]
My business partner made this herself.
It's 100% handmade strawberry jam.
As of now, I refuse to talk to anyone
who didn't receive one.
- [zipper closing]
- [fast squeak]
[chuckles]
Are you saying she made this…
For him?
Mi-ji! That's not right.
You can't do this to me.
I just made it with the strawberries
from the farm, though.
But you've never made
anything like this for me.
Make me one too.
Make one using our store's strawberries!
- [Se-jin] We're in public. Quiet down.
- [Gyeong-gu] Make me one too!
[music concludes]
[doctor] No, please don't get up.
[Ro-sa groans]
[doctor inhales]
Fortunately, there's nothing wrong
with your head or your bones.
Ma'am, have you ever been sick before?
[hesitates] Pardon?
You must've been in pain.
Did you have severe abdominal pain…
- Well…
- …or indigestion?
- [soft pensive music playing]
- If you're talking about
the stomach issue I had
when I was younger…
Oh no! Ro-sa!
Ro-sa, are you okay? Oh dear…
[shouting]
Why is no one coming here to help her?
No, I just saw some gallstones on your CT.
- Gallstones?
- [doctor] Yes.
I saw quite a few.
With this many gallstones,
the pain must've been unbearable.
Haven't you gone to see a doctor?
Oh, I…
I just thought it was due to old age.
[breathes deeply]
[woman sobbing]
Ro-sa, hang in there just a little longer.
[breathes shakily]
[Ro-sa groans]
- Surgery?
- [music fades]
They found gallstones
while doing a pelvic CT scan.
So she would've never known
if she hadn't hurt her back.
Hey, this is totally…
A disguise something…
Yes, a blessing in disguise.
It's not a major surgery,
so I got the earliest date possible.
Your friend is also very stubborn.
I told him it's fine, but he kept…
You're not okay.
You were just enduring it.
- Gosh.
- He's right.
You also hurt your back,
so just focus on your recovery
until the surgery.
You two make a great team.
Anyway, given my current situation,
he'll have to go alone
to that meeting we talked about.
It'll be easier
than dealing with an old lady
who doesn't know anything.
So when should I tell my company
you're available?
It doesn't matter to me.
Choose a day that works for you.
A day that works for me?
Then let me ask my team leader and…
Never mind. I'll just call him myself.
Why?
He might yell at you
since you're in the middle of it all.
We're the ones rescheduling,
so I'll tell him.
I can call your team leader, right?
- [Mi-ji] See?
- [quirky music playing]
[Mi-ji] He's making it so obvious
that he still likes Mi-rae.
Why is he pretending otherwise?
[scoffs] First love, my butt.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Why Dusonbong Peak?
- What?
- [music concludes]
I kept thinking about it
after what you told me.
Nothing special really happened
at Dusonbong Peak
for you to have fallen for her.
You wouldn't know.
You stayed at the foot
of the mountain instead of hiking.
But I saw the two of you come down.
- [young Mi-ji grunts]
- [intriguing music playing]
Mi-ji! Ho-su! You brats!
- What took you so long?
- [Mi-ji] Everyone was back except you two.
You showed up right before
the teachers went looking for you.
Did you start liking her
because she helped you come down?
Mi-ji practically carried you down
on her back.
Was it because of a sense
of camaraderie or solidarity?
It happened when we were going up.
What?
I fell in love with her on the way up,
not coming down.
Anyway, I'll call you after we set a date.
What is he talking about?
He went up by himself.
[music concludes]
What could it be?
HOW TO WRITE A PROJECT REPORT
[Mi-ji] There are so many places
that offer to write papers
and personal statements for a fee.
So why aren't there any places
that write reports?
Why is no one willing to write it? Jeez!
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
She threw a fit just over the meeting.
As soon as I mention the project report,
Mi-rae is going to kill me!
[Mi-rae] Just stay put
and don't do anything.
[cries]
Jeez! I'm so screwed!
What am I going to do?
Should I just write whatever I can?
But I need to know the basics
in order to write anything at all.
Damn it! I'm so screwed.
I'm seriously screwed.
What am I going to do?
[cell phone buzzing]
MI-JI
- What?
- [Mi-rae] You're alone now, right?
Why?
Grandma wants to hear your voice.
Talk to her for a minute.
Grandma, I'll go get more blankets.
Grandma!
Goodness, you're going to make
my ears fall off.
Why did you suddenly become a baby?
Grandma, is Mi-rae doing a good job?
Are you okay?
Wait. Did you get your haircut?
[chuckling] Goodness, slow down.
Everything is good here.
Are you doing okay over there?
No, I'm not okay.
I don't know
what I'm doing here right now.
I don't know how to do anything,
but things keep happening.
I'm living on edge every day.
[breathes deeply]
Mi-ji.
Do you remember the promise we made?
- [tender music playing]
- [Wol-sun] Even though you're not here,
I'm holding up my end of the promise.
You will too, right?
- Whatever.
- [Wol-sun chuckles]
Don't ever forget our promise.
I'll call you again.
[cell phone beeps]
[tender music continues]
What promise?
It's a secret.
Jeez.
You two always have secrets of your own.
- [music fades]
- [paper crunching]
KFMC
REFERENCE DOCUMENTS FOR THE NEW HQ
[soft intriguing music playing]
Tae-i, do you have
the documents I requested?
AESIM-DONG LAND LOT SIZE REPORT
[Tae-i] I'm doing them in order.
Tae-i, can you do mine first?
I have to submit this
to the audit office, so I'm in a rush.
I'll do them in order.
Where are you going?
Oh, it's lunchtime.
[employee 1] Ah.
[music fades]
[employee 2] Look at how he talks.
AI is probably more human than he is.
We hired him as a contract worker,
but he's acting all high-and-mighty
just because he's a data analyst!
He's telling us to do it ourselves
if we don't like it.
There's nothing we can do.
He can generate data in just a few hours,
whereas it would take us days to do it.
Beggars can't be choosers.
[intriguing music playing]
Are you okay? I'll do it.
[Mi-ji] Pardon?
I'll finish getting things ready here.
You go check on her.
[intriguing music continues]
It was you, right?
Pardon?
You left this for me, didn't you?
But I never asked you to do it.
So why did you do it
before everyone else's requests?
The CEO visited us recently,
so it seemed more urgent.
But you don't seem to prioritize things
solely based on urgency.
You do them in order.
[sighs]
What are you trying to say?
[whispers] Please help me.
- I can't.
- [music concludes]
I've never even written a report before.
How am I supposed--
I'm not asking you
to write the report for me.
If you just continue to help me
with things like this--
If you need documents, then request them.
You keep saying I helped you,
but providing documents is my job.
I wasn't going out of my way to help you.
You did help me.
You asked me if I was okay,
and you did my work for me.
[sighs] So…
why did you take on this project
after laying low all this time?
Do you even know
who's in charge of the new HQ?
I…
I think I heard it was Mr. Park.
You accepted this project
knowing Mr. Park is in charge?
Anyway, I'm sure you're a pro
when it comes to paperwork.
You've probably written
countless project reports.
So even without my help, you'll--
I can't do it alone.
When someone is forced into a corner,
they become a mess.
They can't function like they usually do.
Don't I sound weird right now?
But you've been doing this for a while.
So I…
I'm sorry, Mi-rae.
To be honest, I'm taking medications,
and I'm getting therapy too.
I cry every day. I can't sleep,
and I also have trouble breathing.
You saw me at the bus stop the other day.
I was sitting there
because I suddenly forgot how to walk.
- [quirky music playing]
- I'm not myself right now.
I really don't want to ask
for a favor like this,
and I know I look weird doing it.
But I really have no one to ask for help.
I mean, I'm asking you
of all people for help.
You just need data?
Yes.
I'll prioritize your data.
Tell me what you need.
Please just give me everything.
What do you mean by "everything"?
Any project reports or documents
that you think seem relevant.
Just give me everything!
Tae-i, are you done with mine yet?
I'm in a rush.
Tae-i, what about mine?
[quirky music continues]
AESIM-DONG 1-GA RESIDENT DEMOGRAPHICS
KPI FEASIBILITY REVIEW
FOR ESG COMPLIANCE
[quirky music continues]
Damn it.
[gasps]
A STUDY ON WAYS TO EXPAND
GREEN SPACES IN REDEVELOPMENT AREAS
TOTAL OF 32 KPIS
"KPI"?
I see.
KEY PERFORMANCE INDICATOR
Given that it was the most critical issue,
we anticipate that
it will positively impact the KPIs too.
KEY PERFORMANCE INDICATOR
Oh, KPI.
[employee] Next is the website management…
KPI.
[quirky music continues]
HOW TO WRITE A TABLE OF CONTENTS
WRITE CONTENT TO MATCH TABLE
TABLE OF CONTENTS
20% OF UNEMPLOYMENT
IS LONG-TERM
Everyone is desperate to get a job.
- [anchor] Twenty percent are unemployed.
- Why would he quit his perfectly good job?
[anchor]
More than half of them are youths…
Who quit?
You didn't hear about it
when you were making jam?
Ho-su quit his job at the law firm.
Ho-su? Why?
How would I know that
when his own mom doesn't?
How could he just suddenly quit
when his mom worked so hard
to support him?
That brat, Bun-hong, used to always brag
about how it's one of the top three
law firms in the country.
[chuckles]
But these days, she's really down.
He must have had a good reason.
Maybe the law firm was the problem.
Even if there was a problem,
it was probably his fault.
You know Ho-su was always like that.
He had a hard time adjusting to school.
He was probably the same at the office.
People who have issues…
always take their issues with them
wherever they go.
Give me that towel.
[Secretary Hwang]
You set up your own firm? Out of the blue?
Where's your office?
I just filed a business registration
to help someone I know.
You? Who is this person?
That crochet lady from before?
I'm telling you,
she and I are just friends.
Your face tells me a different story.
I might receive
a wedding invitation next spring.
[sighs]
She's my first love's twin.
[Secretary Hwang] What?
So you're saying…
that the crochet lady
is your first love's twin?
They look the same?
Yes, they're identical.
Did it work out with your first love?
No, there was nothing like that.
We were just too young.
I see.
You're trying to make it work
with your unrequited first love's twin?
That's a bit strange.
I told you that it's not like that.
There's nothing going on between us,
and I'll make sure it doesn't.
Oh…
You'll make sure it doesn't?
- So there is something between you two.
- There isn't.
So did you ever tell your first love
how you felt?
- No, it was just one-sided.
- Does the crochet lady know?
That her twin was your first love?
- I thought she did.
- Yes.
But now she's acting like she never knew.
That's good.
Then there's nothing stopping you two.
You can go out with the crochet lady now…
Wait. Hold on.
You don't still have feelings
for your first love, do you?
- Pardon?
- [Secretary Hwang] I mean, look at this.
- They look the same.
- [quirky music playing]
[Secretary Hwang]
But you only liked one of them.
She must've been different somehow,
but now you're attracted to the other one.
Has your taste changed?
Or are you looking
for your first love in the other twin?
See, I knew it!
It's important to figure out how you feel.
Things could get weird
if you're not careful.
[clicks tongue] Fine.
At times like this,
there's only one solution.
Since you have nothing to do,
go see for yourself.
Once you see her,
you'll know right away who you like.
[Bun-hong] If you had called me yesterday,
I would've gone grocery shopping.
You came all this way,
but there's not much to eat here.
It's okay.
I'm only here for a short visit.
A short visit? You won't spend the night?
I even cleaned your room.
I have somewhere to go
tomorrow afternoon for work.
I see. You have work.
Why did you buy so much stuff?
You bought two of the same thing.
One is for next door.
Even for your neighbors? My gosh.
- I'll make sure to…
- I'll…
I'll give it to them myself
before I leave.
[quirky music playing]
You will?
Okay.
- [engine pulsing]
- [quirky music continues]
- [engine grinds]
- [Mi-rae] Step on the clutch and--
That's why you should change gears
after you step on the clutch.
[button clicking]
I was surprised
when you asked me for a ride.
Did you want to give me a driving lesson?
There are no tricks or tips
for driving manual.
You just drive every day
and get used to it.
You're so alike.
What do you mean?
I once said you reminded me of someone.
You're just like my grandfather.
- Pardon?
- What's with that reaction?
It is a big compliment.
My grandfather
was my favorite person in the world.
I see.
I mean it.
Grandpa, should I stop over there?
[music concludes]
Well, drive safely.
I will. Oh, wait, the scones!
I got all the ingredients to make scones.
But the oven I ordered has been stuck
at a distribution center for days.
Anyway, as soon as I have an oven,
I'll officially invite you
to an afternoon tea party.
Gosh, it's okay. You don't have to.
[gate closes]
Mi-ji?
[soft music playing]
[music concludes]
You dyed your hair.
It looks good.
Yes, I guess.
So, what brings you here?
I just stopped by my house.
I recently left the firm.
I see.
Who was that earlier?
I've never seen him before.
He's just someone I work with.
Work?
Did you start a new job?
Didn't you say
you had something to tell me?
Oh…
Yes.
It's nothing special.
These days…
I've had a lot of time to think
since I quit my job.
So I've been thinking
a lot about the past.
And it brought back memories
of our time in high school.
By any chance…
do you remember the day
we hiked up Dusonbong Peak?
What?
Dusonbong Peak?
[Ho-su] Yes.
Sometimes…
I still think about the time
we spent together at the top.
[soft daring music playing]
[young Ho-su panting]
[music turns uplifting]
[young Ho-su exhales]
[breathes deeply]
Now that you're here,
there isn't much to see, is there?
So why did you try so hard
to come up here?
[music fades]
Because I don't want to live.
What?
I felt that…
if I couldn't even climb
a mountain like this,
then I would rather die.
[gentle music playing]
Why are you so dramatic?
We should go down now.
[both grunt]
[young Mi-ji] Aren't you hot?
Take it off.
[chuckles softly]
- [gentle pop song playing]
- [singing in Korean]
[singing in Korean continues]
- [leaves rustling]
- [wind whistling faintly]
[singing in Korean continues]
[Ho-su] Looking back now…
I think that was
a turning point in my life.
If I hadn't made it all the way
to the top that day…
I would be a very different person.
I mean, I'm not saying that
I'm doing exceptionally well right now.
[singing in Korean continues]
But I would've turned out even worse.
So, I know it's late…
but I wanted to thank you.
I went all the way to the top that day…
[singing in Korean continues]
…because of you, Mi-ji.
Because of me?
[Ho-su] Yes.
[Mi-rae] I see.
[song concludes]
[soft quirky music playing]
If you have nothing else to say,
should we get going now?
Okay.
I'm sorry I took up your time.
Oh, and take this.
[soft quirky music continues]
[sighs]
Why does she seem
so different from before?
[music concludes]
I'm off now.
Did I keep you from leaving?
No, I still had work to do.
Oh.
Wait.
Have you eaten yet?
We're all doing this to make a living,
so we should eat well.
That chair's broken. You should sit here.
This project was forced on you,
but I guess you still want to do it.
You look way more comfortable than before.
My gosh, have you been observing me?
Why?
- I'll get going now.
- [Mi-ji] Okay, fine.
Gosh, I was just kidding.
Eat before you go.
Here…
I hope you enjoy it.
Mm. It's good.
I'm really curious, though.
Why are you helping me?
I wasn't going to ask,
but I feel a little uneasy
because you're helping me so much.
- Why do you feel uneasy?
- Because I don't know why you're helping.
I'm wondering if you're a spy
sent by Director Choi.
[scoffs]
Isn't it a little too late
to be suspicious?
You're right.
You're going through
way too much trouble to be a spy.
[chuckles softly]
You helped me before.
Pardon?
You may not remember,
but I owe you a big favor.
[intriguing music playing]
[Mi-ji] Mi-rae, you know Kim Tae-i, right?
STRAWBERRY CULTIVATION
- The actress?
- [Mi-ji] No.
- [music fades]
- Tae-i, not Tae-hee.
You know, that contract worker
on your team?
Oh, that person's name is Kim Tae-i?
So?
Did you ever help him?
Or do you know him somehow?
Not at all.
I've never spoken to him before. Why?
This is just my gut feeling.
But I think he likes you.
[sighs] What are you talking about?
That's so random.
Did something happen?
What? No, nothing happened.
It's just that I sensed a romantic vibe.
I told you that I've never spoken to him.
By the way,
I met Ho-su today.
He said he quit his job.
What? He left the firm?
But why did he suddenly show up there?
I don't know. He said he wanted
to talk to me out of the blue.
And he randomly started talking
about Dusonbong Peak.
Dusonbong Peak? What about it?
He just said
that it was a turning point in his life.
He thanked you.
He said he made it to the top
because of you.
Because of me?
Why did he randomly bring that up?
Are you okay?
It was a bit awkward.
I was afraid
that he'd recognize me, but he didn't.
That's not what I meant.
I'm sorry you had to hear that.
I know that you two dated in the past.
[Mi-rae] What?
Are you saying that because of that rumor?
[exhales]
You two came to my race that day,
and you were hugging.
What?
[sighs]
You're talking about the day
you got hurt, right?
I was sick that day.
- You were sick?
- [intriguing music playing]
95TH NATIONAL SPORTS CHAMPIONSHIP
[Mi-rae] I wasn't feeling well,
but I had an academic competition
that day.
Honestly, I don't know
how I even managed to get there.
The others are over there. Let's go.
[sighs]
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I'm fine. It's okay.
[pants]
Mi-rae!
Mi-rae, wake up! Hey!
Hey!
Don't tell them?
Even if you don't want to,
you should tell them that you're sick.
No.
[sighs heavily]
I'll be hospitalized
the moment my family finds out.
I can't tell them until the CSAT is over.
What's the point of taking the CSAT
when you're this sick?
[breathes shakily]
You know how it is.
You know what it means.
You know how crappy it feels
when your body doesn't listen to you.
It's bad enough
that my own body won't listen to me.
I don't need anything else
being out of my control.
So… [breathes shakily]
…don't tell anyone.
Even Mi-ji.
Why…
- [music fades]
- Why didn't you tell me that?
I just told you.
It was a secret until I took the CSAT.
Ho-su didn't tell you after that?
He didn't.
Why didn't you tell me after the CSAT?
You know how things were after the CSAT.
How could I tell you
when you refused to even see me?
[Mi-ji] But…
You could've at least told me later.
[Mi-rae] Why would I
when you never asked about it?
And you were dating Gyeong-gu back then.
I thought you weren't interested in Ho-su.
Did you like him?
No.
Why did Ho-su send mixed signals?
[Mi-rae] You confused him back then.
[Mi-ji] What did I do?
Who knew you'd suddenly
start dating Gyeong-gu?
But Ho-su was very obvious
about his feelings.
He even treated you and me differently.
You had a feeling, didn't you?
Then why was there a rumor
that you two were dating?
[sighs] Is that so important?
I told you it wasn't true.
Is it my job to figure out why
people said that when it's not even true?
No.
That's not what I'm saying.
Why are you suddenly getting upset?
[sighs]
I don't know why.
People just saw what they wanted to
and spread rumors.
[breathes deeply]
Let's stop talking about this. I'm tired.
Okay. Good night.
[cell phone beeps]
[sighs]
[melancholic music playing]
[melancholic music continues]
[Mi-ji panting, groaning]
[groans]
[Mi-ji] That was it?
We ended up like this
over a simple misunderstanding?
[exhales]
I didn't have the courage
to ask about what happened,
so I gave up on my life,
running, and even Ho-su.
What have I been doing?
[breathes deeply]
[music concludes]
Who had a lovers' quarrel?
Mi-ji, Ok-hui's daughter.
She's in a love triangle.
A love triangle? With whom?
You know, the mart owner's son
and the grandson from Changhwa Farm.
They were arguing over Mi-ji.
[imitates growling]
Gyeong-gu threw a fit, demanding
that Mi-ji give him some jam as well.
He ended up on the floor
like a kid throwing a tantrum.
My goodness, in front of everybody?
Goodness, you know how it is
to get into a lovers' quarrel at that age.
- [laughs] You're right…
- Oh my gosh!
Who did she give the jam to?
Pardon?
Who was it?
Enjoy.
What is up with you? Jeez…
Why are you smiling so much?
It seems like the long winter is over
and the flowers are in full bloom
for our dear Mi-ji.
What are you talking about?
I don't know if I should tell you this.
- Whatever. I'm just going to tell you.
- I hope you enjoy your food.
Mi-ji…
[whispers] …has fallen in love.
- What?
- [quirky music playing]
- [giggles]
- Oh, I'm sorry. Enjoy.
What in the world are you talking about?
With whom?
The strawberry farm owner
she's working with.
When you work with someone,
you start developing feelings for them.
That's how I met my husband.
Don't say such ridiculous things.
Why is that ridiculous?
Mi-ji is 30 years old.
She should be dating at her age.
And it seems like
she's found her calling these days.
It would be nice if they got married
and worked on the farm together.
Are you saying those awful things
because she's not your daughter?
Mi-ji doesn't have a lot going for her,
so I should just marry her off,
is that it?
- What are you talking about?
- [Ok-hui] Jeez.
Hey, what's wrong with getting married?
I think getting married
was the best decision I ever made.
If marriage is so wonderful,
then why not marry off your son?
Switch places with me.
[music concludes]
[CEO] This is confidential,
so don't share it with anyone yet.
NEW HQ
AND LRT LINE INTEGRATION
The city has agreed to it.
Whether the project proceeds
as planned depends on that building.
What was it called again?
- Rosa Restaurant, sir.
- [CEO] Right.
The General Affairs Team told me
that there's been some progress.
Yes, we're meeting with the landowner's
legal representative today.
I heard the landowner
was giving us trouble.
But I guess things worked out,
seeing as you're having a meeting.
- Who's in charge of it?
- [intriguing quirky music playing]
Me, sir.
You're in charge?
It's my department's job.
So I should be responsible for it
from start to finish.
Okay. I trust you'll do well.
Do well on this,
and you may get promoted this time.
Yes, I'll do my best.
- Mr. Shin.
- Yes, sir.
Please tell the General Affairs Team
not to attend today's meeting. I'll go.
- [Gyeong-min] You're going, sir?
- Yes. Is the room ready?
Uh…
I was just about to…
Why haven't you started yet?
Look at the time.
Everyone, get the meeting room ready!
Yes, sir. Get it ready.
[music concludes]
What's wrong with Director Choi today?
What's he up to?
[whispers] You don't have
any hacking skills, do you?
I think I can go steal a cell phone.
[scoffs]
Wow…
Mi-rae got her claws into a kid this time.
[employee 1] If she's smart,
she should avoid married men.
I'm sure she doesn't want
to get slapped again at Gwanghwamun.
[employee 2] Right.
[employee 1] How did she manage
to seduce that guy when he's like a robot?
You know she's an expert at that.
She pretends to have feelings for you,
only to abandon you once you're useless
and then play the victim.
Women like her
are a disgrace to the rest of us.
[intriguing music playing]
Do you know that statement
could get you up to five years in prison
or a ten-million-won fine?
Pardon?
Publicly stating false facts
about a specific individual constitutes
the crime of defamation under Article 307,
Paragraph 2 of the Criminal Act.
If this falls under workplace harassment,
then a civil lawsuit may be possible too.
We were just talking to each other.
How is that a public statement?
But I heard you.
- [employee 2] What the hell?
- [Mi-ji] Come in.
- Oh. Ho-su--
- [music concludes]
My name is Lee Ho-su.
I'm Ms. Ro-sa's legal representative.
Where should I sit?
Ah, okay.
Please come this way.
When you look at the first page--
If you read it, I'm sure you'll see
that the proposed amount is nearly 40%
higher than the local market average.
Yes.
As for the retail spaces
within the new headquarters--
We also plan
to guarantee the landowner priority
for leasing a retail space,
if that is her preference,
so she may continue operating
her current restaurant.
Exactly who is in charge of this matter?
It's me.
[Ho-su] Ah.
So, you're Director Choi.
It's the same proposal
you sent last time, isn't it?
Yes. Probably.
My client has stated that
she won't sell under these terms.
From our standpoint, these terms
are already pushing the limits.
Other landowners who've already sold
may even complain if they find out.
Doesn't that mean that it's a site
that you need to secure,
even if it means
you have to go beyond your limits?
- Yes, then…
- [suspenseful music playing]
Are there any additional terms
you would like?
That's something you should propose.
Persuading the landowner isn't my job.
I see. Then we'll continue
to visit her and…
And my client feels uncomfortable
with negotiations
that try to sway her emotionally
through individual employees.
From now on, I kindly request
that only Director Choi, who is in charge,
convey the company's official stance
directly through me,
Ms. Ro-sa's representative.
Yes, of course. [exhales]
[Tae-gwan exhales]
[elevator chimes]
[music builds]
- [music concludes]
- [Mi-ji] Hey, Ho-su!
Ho-su.
You were just going to leave
without saying goodbye?
Bye.
Oh! That's all you have to say?
Why did you follow me in here?
What if someone sees us?
Who cares if they do?
No good will come
from anyone seeing us together.
Let's keep our personal
and work lives separate.
Is that what you were doing
when you took my side earlier?
[hesitates] What do you mean?
Didn't you help me earlier?
Why would I help you?
Why are you suddenly getting annoyed?
I was just thanking you.
[elevator chimes]
[Mi-ji] Hey!
What's wrong with him?
[cell phone buzzes]
TEA PARTY AT CHANGHWA FARM
TOMORROW AFTERNOON
[chuckles softly]
Who are you texting?
The strawberry farm owner.
[Bun-hong] Mi-ji has fallen in love.
The strawberry farm owner
she's working with.
How old is the strawberry farm owner?
Is he pretty old?
I've never asked, so I don't know.
How could you not even ask that?
Jeez.
You need to be able
to take care of yourself
before dating or getting married.
Relying on a man
just because your future looks uncertain
is one of the quickest ways
to ruin your life.
You don't have to look far.
I'm living proof of what happens.
Do you want to end up like me?
Why are you suddenly talking about this?
I hear you're seeing
the strawberry farm owner.
No wonder you've stuck
with this job for so long!
Is it because you're dating him?
Are people saying that?
Is it not true?
Is that just a false rumor?
They're already saying I am,
so does my response even matter?
Stop playing games with me.
Is it true or not?
It's not true.
It's not?
[sighs] Jeez, I knew it.
These ridiculous stories are made up
by people with nothing better to do.
- Goodness.
- [Mi-rae] You believed them.
I didn't believe them.
It's just that there's never been a rumor
about you and a man before.
So I thought there might be
something going on.
[overlapping echoing chatter and laughter]
- [chatter stops]
- [somber music playing]
Mi-ji, why aren't you eating?
[somber music continues]
[hyperventilating]
[breathes deeply]
[music continues, turns ominous]
[Tae-gwan] It's confidential information,
so make sure it doesn't get leaked.
As you can tell, that restaurant
is the key to our new HQ project.
But the landowner has suddenly appointed
a legal representative, so…
But there's not much we can do
since the landowner doesn't want to sell.
Oh?
Her legal representative is Mr. Lee Ho-su.
Do you know him?
[lawyer] Yes,
he used to work at our law firm.
Are you just looking for assistance
in purchasing Rosa Restaurant?
Yes, do you have any way…
Give me all the information
you have concerning this case.
I'll take this on.
[chuckles softly]
[music concludes]
[fire crackling]
[whispers, in English] Okay, okay.
[plate scrapes]
[in Korean] Oh, welcome.
Please come this way.
Should I take your hat?
I…
I quit.
I went overboard, didn't I? I'm sorry.
Please have a seat.
[soft music playing]
Wait. You're really quitting?
Just like that?
Why? Did I do something wrong?
No, it's nothing like that.
But you didn't say anything yesterday.
We've just planted the strawberries,
and they're growing steadily.
We also need to work on the tarp.
I can't do it all by myself.
[Mi-rae] I'm sorry.
Wait. Hold on.
At least tell me why.
Even if you're a temporary worker,
we've been working together for a while.
- If you tell me the problem--
- [Mi-rae] It's my problem.
Thank you for everything.
[music fades]
NEW HQ PROJECT REPORT
Sir, here's the new HQ project report.
[paper stack thuds]
[scoffs]
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
Pardon?
Look at these sentences. Hmm?
[pensive music playing]
The bullet points don't align either.
All the tables have different units.
Some are in thousands and some aren't.
And why didn't you cite your source here?
Who submits a report like this to the CEO?
Did you just wing this
because you didn't want to do it?
Or is this the best you can do?
I'm sorry. I was a bit careless
because I was in a hurry.
You were careless? So you did wing this?
Take it.
I'm sorry. I'll fix it right away and--
[Gyeong-min] Forget it.
I'll fix it, so give me
the original file and the raw data.
You should've just passed this
onto me sooner.
What were you doing until now?
Are you trying to make my life harder?
Go.
[pensive music continues]
[Gyeong-min sighs]
RAW DATA
UNPROCESSED DATA
[music fades]
I WILL BE TAKING A SHORT BREAK
DUE TO HEALTH ISSUES
[Ho-su] Yes, ma'am.
I took a look around the restaurant.
Everything is fine.
Don't worry.
I hope your surgery goes well tomorrow.
- After the surgery, I…
- [knocking on door]
[door sliding open]
[Ji-yun] Is the restaurant closed again?
Yes, the owner is sick, so…
Ho-su.
Thanks.
- Thanks for the drink.
- Try this.
This is their signature drink.
It's okay. I'll drink this…
[Ji-yun] Come on. Give that to me.
This is my drink. Hurry up and try it.
- [coughs]
- [chuckles]
Hmm. It's good.
You always drink Americanos, don't you?
Drinks like this are fun.
You should try them sometimes.
Anyway, why did you come
to the restaurant?
- For work?
- [Ji-yun] Yes.
Our next theme is retro.
I went there a few times
to bring Ms. Ro-sa on board.
I never expected to see you there, Ho-su.
Did Mi-rae ask for your help?
- Mi-rae?
- [Ji-yun] Yes.
Didn't she ask for your help
because she was busy?
Mi-rae's great-aunt runs that place.
- Great-aunt?
- Yes.
You didn't know?
[scoffs]
I didn't know.
I'm the owner's legal representative.
I see.
I just assumed you were there
because of Mi-rae.
Why?
It's not like that.
Well, you two are always together.
And you also arrived
at the high school reunion together.
Plus, back in the day, there was a rumor
that you two were dating.
I wanted to ask you about that.
Why did that rumor start?
That's because…
you two gave off similar vibes
and you seemed so alike.
You always hung out together
and skipped school on the same days.
That's because we were the only ones
in the academic competition prep class…
Anyway, we didn't date.
Then what about now?
- What do you think of Mi-rae now?
- [coughs]
[soft pensive music playing]
Are you interested in anyone?
[soft pensive music continues]
[exhales]
[Mi-ji breathing deeply]
[Tae-i] What are you doing by yourself?
Oh…
- [music fades]
- [Mi-ji chuckles softly]
[slurring] I'm so sorry that things
turned out this way
even after you helped me.
Why did you do that earlier?
What do you mean?
The report…
You didn't wing it.
You worked hard on it
day and night, so why…
I didn't want him to know.
Know what?
That I did my best.
If that were the best I could do,
I'd feel so small and pathetic.
- [inhales deeply]
- [soft music playing]
That's why I lied
about not giving it my all.
I thought it'd be better for him
to think I'm lazy than incompetent.
[sighs] Even though I made a promise…
You're not yourself right now, though.
But you managed to do all that on your own
despite what you're going through.
- [glass sets down]
- I know, right?
To be honest,
it's a miracle that I managed
to even make that report.
But no one knows that.
Yes.
They shouldn't know.
If you're having a hard time…
[sighs]
…why don't you take a short break?
If you rest a little
and take some time for yourself…
[inhales sharply]
Absolutely not.
That's really dangerous.
That's how I ended up
holing myself up in my room.
Holed up?
Don't even get me started.
Once you go in there,
it's so hard to come out.
So how did you get out?
How did I get out?
[chuckles softly]
My grandma…
asked for me.
[Ok-hui] Mi-ji.
[soft music continues]
Mi-ji.
Grandma keeps asking for you.
She can't even walk now.
[breathes shakily]
She's bedridden.
You need to go see her.
She said she has something to tell you.
So she'll be waiting for your visit.
[breathing deeply]
[sniffles, sobs]
I somehow managed to go out
on the day she collapsed.
[music fades]
But I couldn't bring myself
to keep going out
just because I did it once.
I was such an idiot.
[Mi-ji breathing shakily]
[sobs]
But all of a sudden,
for some reason, I thought of someone.
[young Ho-su] I felt that…
[melancholic music playing]
…if I couldn't even climb
a mountain like this,
then I would rather die.
[Mi-ji sobs, sniffles]
So I thought to myself,
"If I can't even go see Grandma today…
then I should just die."
[sobbing] Yesterday is over.
Tomorrow is yet to come.
Yesterday is over.
And so…
A trip that would usually take me
30 minutes on foot…
It…
took me…
four hours for me to get to her.
[music turns uplifting]
[breathes shakily]
[weakly] Oh!
Grandma!
- Grandma…
- [Wol-sun] My goodness, sweetie.
I knew you'd come.
[stuttering] I knew you would, sweetie.
I'm sorry, Grandma. It's my fault.
[Wol-sun] It's not your fault, Mi-ji.
I asked you to come
so I could tell you that.
Now that I'm bedridden,
I finally understand how you feel.
[sobbing] I'm old, but I'm scared too.
So I can only imagine how scary
and difficult it must've been for you.
- [sobs]
- [Wol-sun] But you know,
I've realized something
now that you're here.
Just like your name means "unknown,"
we don't know yet.
[sobs]
[Wol-sun] Yesterday is over.
Tomorrow is yet to come.
But today is yet unknown, Mi-ji.
So…
let's live today.
I'll do my best to live somehow.
So I want you to live too.
[Mi-ji] Yes…
Promise me…
that you'll never run away from anything.
now.
[sobs]
[Wol-sun] Together,
let's endure one day at a time.
[sobbing] Yes.
- [sniffles]
- [uplifting music continues]
From that day,
I've endured one day at a time
and made it to today.
- I had no idea.
- [music concludes]
I didn't know you'd been through so much.
[chuckles] What's the point, though?
I promised her
that I wouldn't run away from anything.
But I broke that promise today.
You didn't break your promise.
You didn't run away,
and you submitted the report.
I lied.
I could've just said,
"I'm sorry."
"Even though I did my best,
this is all I can do."
But… I lied.
No one knows that, though.
That you lied.
But I know.
[pensive music playing]
To be honest, I got a bit hopeful today.
[sniffles]
It's been a while since I've put
all my effort into something.
I should've expected
that I wouldn't do well.
But I really wanted to do a good job.
So I guess I didn't want to find out
that this is all I am.
[voice trembling] But…
I can't fool myself.
[sniffles]
I should just accept it.
But I can't.
That's why I've spent my whole life
running away like this. I'm an idiot.
[sobs]
[pensive music continues]
[Mi-ji sobbing]
[music fades]
[Ho-su] Thank you for the ride.
I'll see you later.
Wait, Ho-su.
Here.
And this too.
What's all this?
I collected these souvenirs
from the restaurants I covered.
There's a lot of interesting food,
so try one at a time.
You didn't have to.
Thanks.
How was today?
Didn't you have fun going to new places
and trying new foods with me today?
Yes, I got to experience new things,
thanks to you.
Then…
can I call you again?
You don't need my permission for that.
[chuckles]
Let's see each other again.
I'll make sure that you have
a really good time, Ho-su.
[door lock beeping]
- [door opens]
- [door lock chimes]
- [door closes]
- [Tae-i] I'm home.
[door lock chimes]
[suspenseful music playing]
About Ms. Yu…
I think I should keep helping her.
I think I have to.
[suspenseful music continues]
[music concludes]
PLEATED SEA SQUIRT SSAM-JEOT
MINT CHOCOLATE HIGHBALL
[cell phone buzzing]
YU MI-RAE
[cell phone continues buzzing]
MISSED CALL
YU MI-RAE
[cell phone buzzing]
What is it?
[Mi-ji slurring] Hey! Ho-su!
Come out!
[quirky music playing]
[Mi-ji elongating] Ho-su…
Come out.
Hello?
- Mi-rae.
- Where…
[Mi-ji] Oh?
You…
Oh, hey!
[music concludes]
Why are you so drunk?
Jeez. Hey.
When a woman's dealing
with work and life,
there are days
when you get drunk like this,
and there are days when you get upset.
You should've gone home if you were drunk.
Why did you come here?
Why, you little…
Hey, Ho-su. Are you going
to keep treating me like this?
What did I do?
[Mi-ji] Hmm…
You jerk.
You keep confusing me,
sending me mixed signals.
When did I ever do that?
"When did I ever do that?"
My gosh.
- [tender music playing]
- Hey, you know what?
I found it a bit odd when you started
talking about your first love.
If you like Mi-ji,
why can't you just tell me
why you like her?
Why were you going on
about Dusonbong Peak instead?
Are you playing Twenty Questions
with me right now?
Why…
are you curious about that?
You made me curious.
Hey, and another thing…
You definitely went up
to Dusonbong Peak by yourself.
So…
So how could you have fallen for her
when you were going up?
What do you mean by that?
You really…
Explain yourself.
Explain exactly what you meant.
Jeez…
[music concludes]
[sighs]
Well?
Mi-ji wasn't there.
What?
[soft pensive music playing]
[Ho-su] That day…
- I was the last one to the top.
- [student 1] Hang in there, Ho-su.
You're doing great.
You're almost there, Ho-su.
- [Ho-su] I was the only one going up.
- Hang in there, Ho-su.
[student 2] Just a little more, Ho-su.
[student 3] You're almost there.
[Ho-su] Later on,
I saw no one else coming down.
And I was alone.
To be honest, I was so tired.
I thought about giving up
and going back down several times.
But I kept going up…
because I didn't see Mi-ji…
among the people coming down.
[tender music playing]
[Ho-su]
I didn't even have faith in myself.
But she kept waiting,
believing that I'd come.
That's what Mi-ji did for me.
[tender music continues]
[Ho-su] I went up there because of Mi-ji.
If I'd been alone,
I would've never made it to the top.
That's why I fell for her,
because I kept thinking about her
while I was going up.
Me too.
You… What?
[music fades]
I went out that day
because I was thinking about you.
I…
I liked you too.
[gentle pop song playing]
[singing in Korean]
[singing continues in Korean]
YU MI-JI
[Chung-gu]
Who's in charge of Rosa Restaurant?
About the new HQ project.
I heard you might step down.
If I took him out of the picture,
would you take the lead?
[Ok-hui] It's just that she's been
down all day. She even quit the farm.
Why don't you take her out
for some fresh air or something?
You basically kidnapped me in your car.
You really shouldn't cross the line.
You're not Mi-ji, are you?
What do you think of Ho-su?
I want to give it a shot with him.
[Mi-ji] It's like I've lost
before the fight began.
Who are you going to go see?
She's not Mi-rae.
[singing continues in Korean]
Subtitle translation by Jane Jung